## AKPAN, VICTORIA DAVID

## Front-end Web Developer

Phone: +2347087040050 | Email: veedahv55@gmail.com | GitHub: github.com/veedahv | LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/victoria-akpan | Twitter: https://twitter.com/me\_veey

### **PROFILE**

I am a front-end web developer who specializes in creating fast and accessible websites. I reproduce replicas of designs using appropriate front-end technologies. I have experience working with and possess good knowledge of the following:

SKILLS - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, VueJS, Bootstrap, git

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Front-End Intern - Ustacky

December 2020 - till date

- I implemented designs using web technologies like HTML, CSS JavaScript, VueJs, Bootstrap.
- I mentor students and help students where they need help.

## Code Reviewer - Ustacky

December 2020 - till date

• I review students' code and provide valuable feedback and advice.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Front-End Intern - Ustacky

December 2020 - till date

• I implemented an e-commerce website design integrated with Paystack test payment method.

## Web Development - The Roothub

August - October 2020

- Created a shopping list app.
- Created a weather app.
- Created an e-commerce dashboard for an online store.

### Responsive Web Design – FreeCodeCamp

August 2020

- Built a survey form.
- Built a tribute page.
- Built a Personal Portfolio webpage.
- Built a product-landing page.
- Built a Technical Documentation page.

# **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

# Front-End Developer – GiveCampMemphis

February 2021

• I helped rebuild the mobile view of The Women Advocacy Center Site.

# **AWARDS**

• Finalist at the Enye hackathon(2020)